Guide to the Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive,
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Afrika Bambaataa hip hop archive, circa 1972-2016.
8094
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-
600 cubic feet.
Vinyl records and other A/V Recordings, Financial Records, Manuscripts, Memorabilia, Photocopies, Photographs, Printed Materials, Publications.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
BIOGRAPHICAL NOTE
Afrika Bambaataa is an American disc jockey, singer, and songwriter from the South Bronx, New York. Often called the “Godfather” of Hip Hop, Bambaataa has helped to define Hip Hop since it emerged in the South Bronx in the 1970s. One of a handful of Hip Hop's 1970s originators, Bambaataa gave Hip Hop its name, and was the first to define its core artistic elements - DJing, rapping, break dancing, and graffiti art - under one cultural umbrella. His cultural organization, the Universal Zulu Nation, has helped to spread Hip Hop culture throughout the world. His genre-defining 1982 song "Planet Rock" and subsequent electro-funk tracks have become icons of hip-hop and electronic music. In 2007 he was nominated for induction into the Rock and Roll Hall of Fame.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Approximately 40,000 sound recordings representing Bambaataa's music collection from the 1970s to the present. The archive also includes books, documents, and files relating to the founding and spread of the Universal Zulu Nation; and videos, papers, and clothing.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Afrika Bambaataa, 1957-; Universal Zulu Nation (Organization)
Subjects:
African American youth -- Social life and customs.; Disc jockeys.; Electronic music.; Funk (Music).; Hip-hop.; Hip-hop -- Influence.; Hip-hop -- History. -- United States; Music -- Social aspects.; Race relations.; Rap (Music); Rap (Music) -- Political aspects.; Rap musicians.; Hip-hop -- New York.; Rap (Music) -- New York.; Hip-hop; Rap (Music); Rap musicians; Social history
Places:
Bronx (New York, N.Y.) -- Social conditions -- 20th century.; New York (State) -- New York; New York (State) -- Bronx; United States
Form and Genre Terms:
History
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Access to collection restricted until completion of processing, with the exception of vinyl records that have been individually cataloged.
SERIES LIST
Series I. Manuscripts
a. School Papers and Assignments
b. Africa Trip
c. Soul Scrapbooks and Music Writing
d. Notebooks and Miscellaneous Manuscripts
e. Lyrics and Poems
f. Bronx River Neighborhood Center
g. Phone and Contact Lists
Series II. Flyers
Series III. Photographs
Series IV. Personal Papers
a. Personal Papers
b. Press About Bambaataa
c. Catalogs and Mail
Series V. Universal Zulu Nation Documents
a. Infinity Lessons
b. Administration
Series VI. Stage Costumes and Clothing
Series VII. Periodicals and Publications
a. Small Press Publications
b. Periodicals
c. Publications from 3410 De Reimer Ave. Bronx, NY
d. Other Publications
Series VIII. Moving images and audio recordings
a. Video cassettes
a. Audio cassettes
Series IX. Music collection
12 inch vinyl
Sureshots and altered/obscured
Numbered by Bambaataa
Annotated, not numbered (Alphabetical by artist)
A-D
E-H
I-L
L-O
P-S
T-Z
Numbers, unknown and various
Second alpha sequence
Cataloged individually
Not annotated (Alphabetical by artist)
A
B
C
D
E
F
G
H
I
J
K
L
M
N
O
P
Q
R
S
Afrika Bambaataa recordings
Renegades of Rhythm Tour
Test pressings and white labels (not yet cataloged)
Compilations (not yet cataloged)
7 inch vinyl
Numbered (not yet cataloged)
Annotated not numbered (not yet cataloged)
No annotations (not yet cataloged)
Acetates and lacquer discs
Cassettes (not yet cataloged)
CDs (not yet cataloged)
Series X. Ephemera
CONTAINER LIST
- Series IX. Music collection
  - 12 inch vinyl
    - Renegades of Rhythm Tour
      Series contains vinyl discs that were selected by DJ Shadow and DJ Cut Creator and played on their Renegades of Rhythm tour.
      Arranged by Box number.
      - DJ Shadow selections., Expression; SR-6714; DJ Shadow. (Box 1)
        Sugar Hill Records
        Englewood, New Jersey
      - Turntables by the Bay. Vol. 1: (all that scratchin' is makin' me bitch)., 2001; SR-6715 (Box 1)
        Warner Brothers Records
        Burbank, California
      - Skip-proof scratch tool. Volume 2, 1999; SR-6716-6717; DJ Swamp (Box 1)
        Blunt Recordings
        New York, New York
      - Etchings of the upper dynamic frequencies, 1999; SR-6718; DJ Quest (Box 1)
        Matrix etching side A: "NOT RECOMMENDED" side B "...FOR SUCKER DJ'S"_x000D_
        Reflection Records
        New York
      - Live in New Orleans, 1981; SR-6719-6720; Beverly, Frankie. (Box 1)
      - Bionic booger breaks, 1994; SR-6721; Darth Fader (Musician) (Box 1)
        Matrix etching side 1: "Trm boogers with rice and spit"._x000D_ Matrix etching side 2: "Jimi Hendrix liv
        Brunswick Records
      - Cut Chemist suite: featuring hip hop remixes., 1998; SR-6722 (Box 1)
        For promotional use only; not for sale._x000D_
      - Mexican, 1984; SR-6723; Jellybean (Musician) (Box 1)
        Tommy Boy
      - Vintage funk jams!, 2002; SR-6724; Jimmy Castor Bunch. (Box 1)
        Decca
      - What's the name of this nation?...Zulu, 1993; SR-6725; Time Zone (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Test pressing PRO-07409
        Nezzie Music: Super 7 Records
      - King of rock, 1985; SR-6726; Run-D.M.C. (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Promotional copy.
        TSOB
        Brooklyn, New York
      - King of rock, 1985; SR-6727; Run-D.M.C. (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Capitol Records
        Hollywood, California
      - Let's get small, 1982; SR-6728; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 1)
        EMI: Eco Music
        France
      - Let's get small, 1982; SR-6729; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Debut Records
        England
      - Raptivity, 1980; SR-6730 (Box 1)
        RCA/BMG Heritage
      - Raptivity, 1980; SR-6731 (Box 1)
        MCA: Universal Music & Video Distribution
        Santa Monica, California
      - Funk you!, 1985; SR-6732; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 1)
        Hip Hop Records
        Ft. Lauderdale, Florida
      - Once in a lifetime; Born under punches; Houses in motion, 1980; SR-6733-6734; Talking Heads (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Promotional copy from the Sire Album SRK 6095, Remain in light.
        Scratchables
        United States
      - Warm heart cold steel, 1976; SR-6735 (Box 1)
        Direction
        St. Laurent, Quebec
      - Warm heart cold steel, 1976; SR-6736 (Box 1)
        Prodigal
      - Scratch & win, 2004; SR-6737; West, Supa Dave (Box 1)
        Profile
      - Express yourself; Have a good time, 1977; SR-6738; New York Community Choir. (Box 1)
      - Black President, 1981; SR-6739; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 1)
      - Drumbeat, 1974; SR-6740; Ingram, Jim. (Box 1)
      - Good times; A warm summer night, 1979; SR-6741-6742; Chic (Musical group) (Box 1)
        "Promotional copy - not for sale"
        Westbound Records
        Detroit, Michigan
      - Bounce, rock, skate, roll, 1979; SR-6743; Mason, Vaughan. (Box 1)
        Almo Sounds
      - Bounce, rock, skate, roll, 1979; SR-6744; Mason, Vaughan. (Box 1)
        D.E.T.T. Records
        Landover, Maryland
      - Stand!, 1969; SR-6745; Sly & the Family Stone (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Epic: E 26456 (on container: PE 26456)._x000D_
        D & M Sound
      - Greedy special in store disco pak., 1977; SR-6746 (Box 1)
        Salsoul Records
      - Dance to the drummer's beat; Easy going, 1978; SR-6747; Herman Kelly & Life (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Island Records
      - Message II (survival)., 1982; SR-6748; Melle Mel. (Box 1)
      - Ooh baby, 1982; SR-6749; West Street Mob (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Sire Records
      - Ooh baby, 1982; SR-6750; West Street Mob (Musical group) (Box 1)
        RCA Victor
      - Def jam; Cold chillin' in the spot, 1985; SR-6751; Jazzy Jay. (Box 1)
        Sure shot pub. by Def Jam--Label.
        Respect
        Memphis, Tennessee
      - Optimo., 1983; SR-6752 (Box 1)
      - Messin' around; Bring it here, 1981; SR-6753; Wild Sugar (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Promotion copy
        Arista Records
        London, England
      - Funkadelic, 1975; SR-6754; Funkadelic (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Nine Nine Records
      - Play at your own risk (Vocal); Rock at your own risk (Instrumental), 1982; SR-6755-6756; Planet Patrol (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Promotional copy; not for sale._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (Runout Side A): HERbiE JR :-) FK *ANgiE AN ENDLESS SMASh!! TB-825-A Vocal Matrix / Runout (Runout Side B): HERbiE JR :-) TB-825-B Instrument
      - Flowers of romance, 1981; SR-6757; Public Image Ltd. (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Matrix etchings: BSK-1-3536 LW1; BSK-1-3536 LW3. Both sides contain stamped asterisk.
        Atlantic Records
      - Flowers of romance, 1981; SR-6758; Public Image Ltd. (Musical group) (Box 1)
        Enterprise Records
      - Sing sing; The good, the bad and the ugly, 1978; SR-6760 (Box 1)
      - Special 12 inch disco mix., 1978; SR-6760 (Box 1)
      - Bambaataa's theme; Tension, 1986; SR-6789; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 1)
        Promotional copy._x000D_
      - Change the beat, 1982; SR-6727; Fab 5 Freddy, 1959- (Box 2)
        T.K. Disco
        Hialeah, Florida
      - Dogs of War, 1977; SR-6759; Dogs of War (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Grand Awards Records Co.
      - Shangri-la, 1978; SR-6763-6764; Pregunta (Musical group) (Box 2)
      - Get out of my mix: (special dance version); Get on out of my mix: (special dub version), 1983; SR-6766; Dolby, Thomas, (Box 2)
      - Adventures of Grandmaster Flash on the wheels of steel., 1981; SR-6767 (Box 2)
        Tommy Boy Music
      - Zulu Nation throw down. Volume #2: (Soul Sonic Force)., 1978; SR-6768-6769 (Box 2)
        Vermack Records
        Washington D.C.
      - Can I get a soul clapp "fresh out of the pack"; Hey what's your sign, what's your name, what's on your mind, 1982; SR-6770; Grand Wizard Theodore. (Box 2)
        The group name misspelled on label. Should read: The Fantastic Romantic 5._x000D_ Stamped in dead wax: Mastering FRANKFORD/WAYNE NEW YORK._x000D_ SOUL WAX #860-0097 DISCO-WAX--Label.
        Def Jam Recordings
      - Magnificent seven; Lightning strikes (not once but twice); One more time; One more dub, 1980; SR-6772; Clash (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Celluloid
      - Perfect beats. Vol. 1: New York electro hip-hop + underground dance classics: 1980-1985., 1998; SR-6774 (Box 2)
        Compilation of material originally released 1977-1982.
        Free Spirit
      - Knock him out, Sugar Ray; E.U. Freeze, 1980; SR-6776; EU (Musical group) (Box 2)
      - Party scene, 1983; SR-6777; Russell Brothers (Rap group) (Box 2)
        Generation Records
      - Message, 1982; SR-6778; Grandmaster Flash. (Box 2)
        Gold Mind Records: Distributed by Salsoul Records
      - This is madness, 1971; SR-6779; Last Poets (Group) (Box 2)
        Paul Winley Records
      - Remember to remember; To the unknowledgeable one., 1981; SR-6780 (Box 2)
        Jet Records
      - Play that beat, Mr. D.J., 1983; SR-6781 (Box 2)
        Capitol Records: Venice in Peril Records
      - Last night a D.J. saved my life, 1982; SR-6782; Indeep (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Promotional copy._x000D_ Sure Shot mix by Tony Humphries.
        Sound of New York
      - Jive rhythm trax., 1982; SR-6783; Willesden Dodgers (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Groove Time Records
        San Bernardino, California
      - Can you feel it?; Knowledge me, 1986; SR-6784; Original Concept (Musical group) (Box 2)
      - Album, 1985; SR-6785; Mantronix (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Promo copy; not for sale._x000D_
        Soul Wax Inc.
      - Trans-Europe express, 1977; SR-6786; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Epic
      - Kool & deadly (Justisizms)., 1987; SR-6787 (Box 2)
        DJM Records
      - Sure boys (dance mix); The anvil (dance mix), 1982; SR-6788; Visage (Musical group) (Box 2)
        Sleeping Bag Records
      - Shango funk theology., 1984; SR-6790 (Box 2)
      - Beat goes on, 1984; SR-6791; Cooper, Californiarol (Singer) (Box 2)
        Test pressing of Profile PRO7409._x000D_ Matrix etching: HF Herbie Jr.
        PolyGram Records
      - Fire; Clearly, 1999; SR-6792; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 2)
        White label._x000D_ Issued in white record sleeve._x000D_
        Plutonic Recordings
        Hamburg, Germany
      - Maryknoll World, 1970-1979; SR-6794 (Box 2)
        Timber!
      - Spider-Man; From beyond the grave. Music and lyrics by Stephen Lemberg. Script by Stephen Lemberg, Based on characters created by Stan Lee., 1972; SR-6795; Lemberg, Stephen. (Box 2)
      - What time is it?, 1982; SR-6796 (Box 2)
        1-23701 (on container spine: 9 23701-1)_x000D_ Promotional copy stamped on jacket in gold lettering._x000D_
        Marlin Records; Distributed by TK Productions
        Hialeah, FL
      - Accept no substitutes, 1976; SR-6797; Pleasure (Musical group), (Box 2)
        Buddah Records
      - Billy Squier., 1981; SR-6798-6799; Squier, Billy, 1950- (Box 3)
        Fania Records
      - South Bronx, 1986; SR-6800; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Matrix / Runout (A Side Runout Etched): MKHAN 77 A-1 DAMONT; Matrix / Runout (B Side Runout Etched): MKHAN 77 B-1 DAMONT.
      - Da ultimate B-Boy weapon vol. #1., 1985; SR-6804 (Box 3)
        Beauty and the Beat Records
        Elizabeth, New Jersey
      - Da ultimate B-Boy weapon vol. #1., 1985; SR-6805 (Box 3)
      - Popcorn., 1972; SR-6806; Hot Butter (Musical group) (Box 3)
        B-Boy Records
        S.l.
      - Maybe tomorrow, 1971; SR-6809; Jackson 5 (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Matrix / Runout (A Side Runout Etched): MS-7Z3 P-4129 HS-1843 S-1; Matrix / Runout (B Side Runout Etched): HS-1844P 1130 MS.735.
      - King Kut, 1985; SR-6810; Word of Mouth (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Streetwave: B Boy Records
      - Criminal minded, 1987; SR-6811 (Box 3)
        Side A: Hot-Club-Version; side B: Hot-Dub-Version.
        B Boy Records
      - Wildstyle, 1983; SR-6812; Time Zone (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Matrix / Runout (Etchings side A): CEL-165-A-2 HERbiE JR :v) FK B- 1 Matrix / Runout (Etchings side B): CEL-165-B-2 HERbiE JR :v) FK B- 1.
      - Renegades of funk., 1984; SR-6813 (Box 3)
        Stax Records
      - Looking for the perfect beat, 1983; SR-6815; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 3)
        Musicor Records
      - This is madness, 1984; SR-6816; Last Poets (Group) (Box 3)
        Morningstar Records
      - Blow your head: disco mix, 1989; SR-6817; J.B.'s (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Tommy Boy Records
      - First base, 1973; SR-6820 (Box 3)
      - Optimo., 1983; SR-6821 (Box 3)
        Total Sounds
        Trinidad
      - Messin' around; Bring it here, 1981; SR-6822; Wild Sugar (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Promotion copy; not for sale._x000D_
        Harry J. Records
        Miami, Florida
      - Wattstax: the living word., 1973; SR-6823=disc 1 (Box 3)
      - Get up offa that thing, 1976; SR-6824; Brown, James, 1933-2006. (Box 3)
        Promotional copy; not for sale._x000D_ "Special disco version; for radio programming only"
      - Wild style., 1983; SR-6825 (Box 3)
        All music mixed live from the original record of the motion picture Wild style.
        Polydor Records
      - Greatest beats., 1985; SR-6826=disc 1 (Box 3)
        Promo copy; not for sale.
        Chrysalis Records Ltd.
        United Kingdom
      - Planet rock (backwards), 1982; SR-6827; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 3)
        EMI America
      - I didn't know I loved you (till I saw you rock & roll), 1983; SR-6828; Planet Patrol (Musical group) (Box 3)
        "From the album Planet Patrol TB 1002. "_x000D_Promotional copy; not for sale._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (A-Side Run Out): TB-837-A "It's Hot" Herbie Jr Angie Matrix / Runout (B-Side Run Out): TB-837-B Herbie Jr Other (Stamped In Run Out): MAST
      - Play at your own risk (Vocal); Rock at your own risk (Instrumental), 1982; SR-6829; Planet Patrol (Musical group) (Box 3)
      - Planet rock; Bonus beats 1, 1982; SR-6830 (Box 3)
        Promotional copy; not for sale.
      - Unified rebelution, 1995; SR-6831; Jurassic 5 (Musical group) (Box 3)
        Promotional use only._x000D_ Matrix / Runout (Etching Side A): TVT 5811 A Matrix / Runout (Etching Side B): TVT 5811 B Matrix / Runout (Etchings Both Sides): SP, MCRDS.
      - Mexican, 1984; SR-6832; Jellybean (Musician) (Box 3)
        On container: V-7831 1/2._x000D_ Promotional copy; not for sale.
      - This is it; Time has come, 1982; SR-6793 (Box 4)
        "Unofficial release" "D.J. only!"--Label._x000D_
        Vintertainment
      - Rock the house; Cuttin' Herbie, 1983; SR-6835; B Boys. (Box 4)
        GSF Records
      - Two, three, break., 1983; SR-6837 (Box 4)
      - Drumbeat, 1974; SR-6838; Ingram, Jim. (Box 4)
      - Black Family Day: Bazaar May 27, 1974, 1974; SR-6839; Farrakhan, Louis. (Box 4)
        Old Town
      - South Bronx; The "p" is free, 1986; SR-6840; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 4)
      - South Bronx; The "p" is free, 1986; SR-6840; Boogie Down Productions (Musical group) (Box 4)
      - Greatest beats., 1985; SR-6841=disc 2 (Box 4)
      - Peoples message take two, 1983; SR-6842; Lewis, Terry, 1956- (Box 4)
      - Return to Planet Rock; Inside looking out, 1989; SR-6843; Afrika Bambaataa, 1957- (Box 4)
        Pressed on transparent green vinyl.
        Black Family
        Chicago, Illinois
      - Play at your own risk, 1998; SR-6844; Planet Patrol (Musical group) (Box 4)
      - Lost in the music, 1991; SR-6845; Malibu (Musician) (Box 4)
      - Deep concentration: the future of experimental hip hop., 1997; SR-6846-SR-6847 (Box 4)
      - Bongo rock; Apache., 1973; SR-6848; Incredible Bongo Band. (Box 4)
      - Rap archives legends, volume 1., 1996; SR-6849 (Box 4)
        Farr Records
        Los Angeles, California
      - Disco dance '82 mix., 1982; SR-6850 (Box 4)
      - Life is something special, 1982; SR-6852 (Box 4)
        Event Records
      - Damn right I am somebody, 1974; SR-6853; Wesley, Fred. (Box 4)
        Sounds of Urban London Records; Sounds of Urban London Records
        Beverly Hills, California
      - Please., 1975; SR-6854; Please (Musical group) (Box 4)
        York's Records
      - Mountain live: "the road goes ever on", 1972; SR-6855; Mountain (Musical group) (Box 4)
        Pride Records
      - Let me show you, 1976; SR-6856,SR-6857; Williams, Esther (Singer) (Box 4)
        Invictus
      - Greedy G, 1980; SR-6858; Brentford Disco Set (Musical group) (Box 4)
        People Records
      - Drop the bomb, 1982; SR-6859; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 4)
        Telefunken
      - Konk party., 1983; SR-6860 (Box 4)
        Windfall
      - Change the beat, 1982; SR-6861; Fab 5 Freddy, 1959- (Box 4)
        Fresh Records
      - No sell out, 1983; SR-6862; LeBlanc, Keith. (Box 4)
        Promotional copy, not for sale._x000D_ The voice of Malcom X is taken from various speeches recorded in the early nineteen sixties.
        Studio One
        Kingston, Jamaica
      - Def jam; Cold chillin' in the spot, 1985; SR-6863; Jazzy Jay. (Box 4)
      - Get out of my mix: (special dance version); Get on out of my mix: (special dub version), 1983; SR-6864; Dolby, Thomas, (Box 4)
      - Hip hop, be bop (don't stop); Hip hop, be bop (part 2)., 1982; SR-6865 (Box 4)
        Idlers: Distributed by Warlock Records
      - Tour de France (remix), 1983; SR-6866; Kraftwerk (Musical group) (Box 4)
        Emergency Records & Filmworks
      - Owner of a lonely heart, 1983; SR-6867; Rabin, Trevor, (Box 4)
        "Promotional copy. Not for sale."
        Atco Records
      - Trow the D. and ghetto bass, 1986; SR-6868; Ghetto Style (Musical group) (Box 4)
        Matrix / Runout (Side A Runout Etching): GR-100-A KK Mastering LUKE "SKYY" WALKER IN GOD WE TRUST Matrix / Runout (Side B Runout Etching): GR-100-B KK Mastering GHETTO STYLE DJ.
        LRC
      - Se viste de gala, 1970; SR-6869; Orquesta Flamboyan. (Box 4)
        Cotillion Records
      - Barretto, 1972; SR-6870; Barretto, Ray. (Box 4)
      - Bongo rock; Apache, 1970; SR-6871; Incredible Bongo Band. (Box 4)
        Matrix / Runout (A): AR 1001 A Matrix / Runout (B): AR 1001 B.
        Arawak
        Jamaica
      - Dance to the drummer's beat; Easy going, 1978; SR-6872; Herman Kelly & Life (Musical group) (Box 4)
        Title from disc label.
        Streetalk Records
        Canada
      - Obstination: cadence reggae, 1983; SR-6875; Gospellers International (Musical group) (Box 5)
      - Black President, 1981; SR-6876; Fela, 1938-1997. (Box 5)
      - Drop the bomb, 1982; SR-6878; Trouble Funk (Musical group) (Box 5)
        Inphasion Records
      - Chove chuva, 1977; SR-6879; Samba Soul (Musical group) (Box 5)
        Interscope Records
      - No sell out, 1983; SR-6880; LeBlanc, Keith. (Box 5)
      - Exorcist: damn right I am somebody, 1974; SR-6881; Wesley, Fred. (Box 5)
      - Funky highlife, 1975; SR-6884; Mann, C. K. (Box 5)
      - W.O.E. is me, 2000; SR-6885; Jurassic 5 (Musical group) (Box 5)
        Promotional copy; white label.
        Sesame Street
      - W.O.E. is me, 2000; SR-6886; Jurassic 5 (Musical group) (Box 5)
      - EMI promo: no tricks in 96': it's time to build b-boy vinyl., 1996; SR-6887 (Box 5)
        Promotional release._x000D_
        Roots Production
      - Electric Company., 1974; SR-6888 (Box 5)
      - Hip hop funk dance classics. Volume 1.: featuring the battle of the Cold Crush Brothers verses Grand Wizard Theodore & The Fantastic 5 MC's., 1991; SR-6890 (Box 5)
        QuaMsa International Ltd.
      - Knock him out, Sugar Ray; E.U. Freeze, 1980; SR-6891; EU (Musical group) (Box 5)
      - Flash it to the beat; Fusion beats vol. 2, 1982; SR-6892 (Box 5)
        Music Merchant
      - Mighty, mighty (Mike Tyson); Good old days, 1988; SR-6893; Most Wanted (Rap group) (Box 5)
        Kalinda
        Trinidad & Tobago
      - Straight out of the jungle, 1989; SR-6894-6895; Jungle Brothers. (Box 5)
        Jamtu Records
        Cherry Hill, New Jersey
      - I can't stop; I get a kick, 1976; SR-6896-6897; Davis, John (Conductor) (Box 5)
      - Dance, dance dance (yowsah, yowsah, yowsah); Sa¿¿o Paulo, 1977; SR-6898; Chic (Musical group) (Box 5)
        EMI
      - Message, 1972; SR-6899; Barretto, Ray. (Box 5)
        Famous Flame Records
      - Candido's drum fever., 1973; SR-6900-6901; Candido, 1921- (Box 5)
        Sam Records
        Long Island City, New York
      - Martians visit; Sail on, 1978; SR-6902; Wabine¿¿ (Musical group) (Box 5)
        Emprise; Distributed by Program Records
        Windsor, CT Union, New Jersey
      - Funky highlife, 1975; SR-6903-6904; Mann, C. K. (Box 5)
      - Life, 1973; SR-6905; Exuma. (Box 5)
        Wabine¿¿ Productions
      - Cymande., 1972; SR-6906 (Box 5)
        ICE Records
        Port of Spain, Trinidad
      - Chove chuva, 1977; SR-6907-SR-6908; Samba Soul (Musical group) (Box 6)
      - Let's get high (on the music); Party (any way you wanna), 1978; SR-6910-SR-6911; Nice and Tight Band (Musical group) (Box 6)
      - Good times, 1979; SR-6912; Chic (Musical group) (Box 6)
        Housed in an Atlantic, promotional not for sale sleeve.
        Bozo Meko Records
      - Greatest hits, 1984; SR-6913; Sugar Hill Gang (Musical group) (Box 6)